var questions = [
    {
        question: 'What city was Kanye West born in?',
        choices: ['New York', 'Los Angeles', 'Chicago', 'Atlanta'],
        answer: '3'
    },

    {
        question: 'What movie did Tupac Shakur star in?',
        choices: ['Next Friday', 'Juice', 'Menace II Society', 'Boyz n the Hood'],
        answer: '1'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which rapper became infamous for accidentally shooting himself?',
        choices: ['Lil Wayne', '50 Cent', 'The Notorious B.I.G.', 'Snoop Dogg'],
        answer: '0'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which rapper has won the most Grammy Awards?',
        choices: ['Kendrick Lamar', 'Drake', 'Jay-Z', 'Eminem'],
        answer: '2'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which rapper has the largest net worth as of 2019?',
        choices: ['Sean \'Diddy\' Combs', 'Dr. Dre', 'Kanye West', 'Jay-Z'],
        answer: '3'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the best selling Hip-Hop album as of 2019?',
        choices: ['Marshall Mathers LP by Eminem', 'Life After Death by The Notorious B.I.G.', 'Speakerboxxx/The Love Below by OutKast', 'Licensed to Ill by The Beastie Boys'],
        answer: '2'
    },

    {
        question: 'How many members are there in the Wu-Tang Clan?',
        choices: ['Eight', 'Nine', 'Ten', 'Eleven'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    
    {
        question: 'What is NOT one of the five elements of Hip-Hop?',
        choices: ['Breakdancing', 'Beat Production', 'Graffiti', 'Emceeing'],
        answer: '1'

    },

    {
        question: 'Who is the best selling Hip-Hop artist of all time?',
        choices: ['Kanye West', 'Eminem', 'Drake', '2Pac'],
        answer: '1'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which of these pro athletes does/did NOT have a rap career?',
        choices: ['Steve Largent', 'Clint Dempsey', 'Kobe Bryant', "Shaquille O'Neal"],
        answer:'0'
    }
];